I've got a name of mine, especially, I'm in the United States Council.
I'm a two public input and personal affairs and I wish to address the council on any of the
gender items.
Then we'll go to the Santa agenda.
Staff is recommending items 4 or 3 or 8 on the Santa agenda.
There's no objection.
We have motion to approve.
So moved.
Second.
Lewis.
I.
Wisconsin.
And I'm recognized mine, a public school, senior football world, I've got your country, don't
be here tonight, but if you just like to start on this thing, tell the two yard, my
position you're playing and we'll just do it that way.
I'm just a child.
I'm very wanted.
We have Lewis.
I'm a clown.
It's right.
Daniel.
What are you saying?
Okay.
Alice?
Yes.
Concerning.
Can you get out of the office of Lutt-Butter, the Mississippi City, flaunting?
Don't be very concerned.
Roger here.
I'm free to charge right in theacker.
I don't know.
I don't know, yeah.
So you know when I'm flying down?
Would you be fighting, buddy, Green?
You're ready to turn it on.
You're good?
You look, guys.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Good.
All right, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I'm Dan Sticks, looking at the world out on our
Co-Naming, these three North East and these three South East,
BJ Town, the Steebons, but we're taking our own
Bervard and Proclamation, and we're going to read a short
bio and we're going to read the Proclamation.
We're going to take our homes, graduate in 1972 from
my high school, there's a conversation with some of his
conferences where Stake Chak and Hardler, Stake
Champing in the Longjaw, and Stake Champing Basketball
in 1972 with the record, 27,000 pre-incressive.
Prep all-American football, point-going-back, and free
safety is a two-time all-American in 1974, in 1975.
As Freshman was named Sugar Bowl in VP, and 132 yards.
Excuse me, bear with me.
Back to give me.
Proclamation, Declaration of Honorary Co-Naming of D-Straight
North East and D-Straight, South East, BJ Town, to Steebons,
Bervard, this Tinker Homes, Bervard, in the city of Miami,
Auto County, Oklahoma.
Whereas my report came real Johnson in my
city council group is important to recognize
citizens who distinguish themselves by various
means and it might be significant contributions to our community.
And the Miami City Council believes the tanker owns is such an individual worthy of being recognized for significant contributions to this community.
And tanker owns is the 1972 graduate of Miami High School, where he competed in football, and tanker owns played football for the University of Oklahoma.
And it was at two-time All-American Library Silver in 1974 and 1975.
Tanker owns was the 1972 Sugar Bowl in B.P.
And tanker owns went on to play six seasons with the New Orleans Act.
Now, therefore, I'd be able to resolve that Mary-Portem, Neil Johnson, in the Miami City Council.
Do you have my weaponized an honorary net renaming of D Street?
Northeastern D Street, Southeastern, B.J. Tonner, to Steve Ones, Board, within the city of Miami, as tanker owns Bolevard.
I guess we need to build them.
Make the most superb?
I'll second it.
Weston.
Hi.
Lewis.
I, Johnson.
Hi.
Jerry, Jim, don't see that coming up.
Never back up.
Good luck at the side of that.
Good luck.
I'm going to take a picture of you all the time.
All right.
Pretty good.
Yeah, it's great.
We'll pass on to take our tankers.
Thanks for all of us.
I'm going to be a part of this.
Mine, the lowest tanker.
Yeah.
That's not told if you would place it.
Family appreciate you.
Thank you, Jerry, Jim.
Thank you for all of us.
On the bottom of the letter, memorandum of understanding between the church and nation in the city of Miami,
regarding the closing of certain city streets into the tribal transportation program.
So, we received a request from the Cherokee Nation.
This stems from the discussions that we had with them over the 1-2-5.
Highway 125 Bridge.
They did not realize I believe it'd be fair to say the extent of the streets that we have on their side of the river.
And so, from that conversation, they're now asking to have many of the streets, city streets,
put into their inventory, which doesn't guarantee us that we will be getting any money to help fix our streets on that side.
can't happen without those being placed into the inventory.
And so, of course, we don't know what's going to be happening with the federal budget
here in the near future, but if you have been on some of the roads that have been dealt
with in the county, for instance, some of the roads around the Peoria Ridge golf course,
you can see the kind of work that they do when they fix a road.
And so, this would be the first step for that to be able to happen here in Miami.
Is this a, we do this every year or just a little bit?
Now, this is the very first time we've done this.
And as the city attorney just indicates, because we've really opened up a conversation with
the Cherokee Nation, a fact that about one quarter of Miami is in the Cherokee Nation.
And doing their due diligence, they recognize, and there were a lot of areas that they
should be serving.
So, they've taken this initiative and were grateful.
Now, the street does not change ownership and it's still our responsibility and all that,
but it can certainly provide some additional assistance and maintenance, and I think it's
something we're very grateful for.
We've got a lot of street to eat, make this.
Oh, yes.
It'll be a little bit of help.
Yeah.
Vicky, I mean, I like the most of it, but I have a second question.
Johnson.
Hi.
Weston.
Lewis.
Hi.
I'm 12, I'm New Business Dean.
Not on this agenda.
Ben.
William.
New.
Yeah.
Staff report.
First staff.
Being then, we go to the mayor council committee announcements, and I had nothing to do
that.
Do not.
City manager's communication.
Well, speaking of street maintenance, I believe that if all goes well, there'll be starting
the micro-surfacing on Thursday.
So, that'll be in a way.
So, looking forward to that project.
Also the focus site, which was the landfill that we used for the Eagle Picture Building.
We think that's about one fourth to three quarters covered right now.
We're still transferring some of the top soil from the spec building in the industrial park there
to finish it out.
And, really appreciate Chief Wallace, allowing us to use that property.
And this is closing it out.
So, it won't be used as a landfill any longer once this is done.
And then, one final thing, the contractor at the old Eagle Picture area is removing the last
of the chat.
They even found more chat and had to do another change order, but they're out there doing that
right now.
And the next step is to install the well and the sun pump.
And then, after that's taken care of, it'll be turned over to us for the splash pad.
So, projects moving a little slower than we have.
It's anticipated, but it is moving.
Yeah, everything is going well there.
So there is no risk of losing our variant.
Now we are keeping up with the state all the time,
and they keep us sharing us everything's okay.
Good.
So, that's my report.
Well, with the risk of breaking records, we're in love here during the night.
Make sure you join.
Second question.
Lewis, I question.
I can't get used to these.
Never pass.
Don't tell them I'm not here without you.
Yeah.
Thank you.